Anjali Maurya

- UX/UI DESIGNER PRODUCT DESIGNER
- Parlin, Germany

EDUCATION

UI Design Certificate

Careerfoundry 2020 – 2021

Intensive course at one of the world's leading UI /UX design schools providing 600+ hours of training with industry-leading tutors and mentors.

Master Of Business Administration (MBA)

United Institute Of Management 2017 – 2019

Comprehensive program combining advanced HR strategies with practical industry insights.

SKILLS

- User experience
- User interface
- App design
- Adaptive web design
- Product design
- Design system
- User research
- AB testing
- User testing

Tools

- Figma
- Adobe UX, Illustrator
- Procreate
- Invision
- Usability hub
- HTML, CSS



- anjimaurya5@mail.com
- in www.linkedin.com/in/anjalimaurya/
- Bē www.behance.net/TheAnjaliMaurya
- dribbble.com/theanjalimaurya

PROFILE

I am a passionate UI/UX Designer with over 3 years of experience and an educational background in a business administration, which gives me a strong understanding of both design and business strategy. I create intuitive and seamless designs that not only enhance user experiences but also align with business goals, ensuring that every project drives value for both users and the company.

EXPERIENCE

UX Designer

Crealytics GmbH, Berlin, Germany

Jul 2023 - Present

- As a mid-level UI/UX designer, I managed end-to-end design processes independently, from user research and wireframing to prototyping and usability testing. This hands-on approach allowed me to effectively balance multiple responsibilities as the product evolved.
- Working independently not only honed my ability to deliver impactful design solutions but also played a pivotal role in expanding my skill set and deepening my expertise in user-centered design.

Junior UX Designer

Crealytics GmbH, Berlin, Germany

Nov 2021 - June 2023

Crealytics is data-activated performance advertising for brands and retailers. They have three products.

Pentaleap

- Joined Crealytics at an early stage when Pentaleap was just beginning to take shape, and played a key role in the development of many features such as Admin Centre, User Settings, Notifications, Platform Tour, etc., bringing unique ideas to the table that helped drive the platform's growth.
- Full update and continued maintenance of the design system to align on new company brand guidelines introduced.

iCLV Dashboard

- Focused on user needs in analyzing customer lifetime value (CLV) through in-depth user research and testing, prioritizing a usercentric approach.
- Defined data visualization style guide and designed dashboards with charts that communicated complex ideas and data in a simple way.

Search Platform

- Led full UX update, redesigning key pages with modern UI components, and worked on new features.
- Enhanced the settings page through card sorting research, improving user experience.